In this video, we are going to discuss
about the stock of ICICI Lombard General Insurance. If we talk about the current price of the stock, then
its current price is 1241 and today almost
we can see the stock
trading at the above level. If we talk about the date percent, then it
is 142 and its 52 clock
is 171. See friends, we recently
made a video on this almost four to five
days ago. Here a W button is being formed,
due to this, the upward movement in the stock can be seen continuing.
If you have not seen this video,
then this video has been uploaded on our channel
5 to 6 days ago, you
must watch that video also. Now see,
here we have come to the technical chart and if we
talk about the time frame, then this is in the one day time
frame, we have set the chart.
Now see,
after the stock reaches the multiple time almost 1100 level, from here
we will see upward movement.  It was seen bouncing right now
and the button is also forming here, almost here,
its target is coming out to 1280,
see, right now the bullishness in the stock is still
pending here, its
target is pending upwards, so due to this,
soon these levels here can become good
and see from here and if it
also bounces upwards, then
we can see even higher levels from here becoming good
and most levels from ₹1360
to ₹1350 can also be seen coming here
soon, if we
talk about the MSD indicator, then the MSC
indicator is also seen giving us bullish signals here,
if your
entry here was downwards then your
stop loss would have been downwards here, but
if you plan a fresh entry here, then
this will not be the right time to
enter from here because your
stop loss will almost be below its neck line, that is,
yours will be below this zone  This sale will be as per the
computer, the target will be very small,
still if you want to take the risk and
want to make an entry on your own, then you
can make an entry, but your first top loss will be
below this, so friends,
now let's go to its tigrative website, from
there check its overview for
cost and what the financial trend of the last four years is
showing,
now we have reached the tigrative website,
after searching the name of the company in the search box, the
left hand side will show you the name of the company and
below it its current price will also be shown, if we
talk about interesting value, then the current
price of more than the intersequelli current
price is more than the intersequelli,
which is a negative point for us, if we
talk about HD rate from Aarohi, then
we see very good returns being generated in the stock even better than the bank rate, if we
talk about dividend, then
we do not get to see it so attractive,
entry point, good time to consider stock is not in
hoverboard, that means you
can plan entry from here because the stock
is not there, the most important thing is
showing whenever you  If you want to
enter any stock, be it short term,
long term, or a swing trade, you should check
your no-rate plug before
making your entry. So, let's now check
its financial trend. As
you can see here,
we are showing data for the last four years from 2019 to 2020. If we
talk about the company's growth, then this
year is very good. We are
seeing growth here, so within this,
we can soon see even higher levels of good growth in the stock. So,
friends, now let's check
what its forecast analysts advise us on
buying. Before proceeding with the video, I
would like to tell you one thing, friends. If
you haven't subscribed to our YouTube channel yet, then
subscribe to the channel. If you liked the
video, then
definitely like the video and also press the bell icon
so that updates of upcoming videos
reach you. So, let's now
check its forecast end list.
What do we give us on buying?
24%, here they are advising us on 71%,
which is quite a lot.  You
can consider good sales, friends, this video has been
made only for educational purpose,
whenever you make an entry in any stock, then
make the entry only after consulting your financial advisor, so this was all
in today's video, we will
meet in the next video with this YouTube
channel, till then take care